[{"answer": "Piers.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Heidi, how are you?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Happy wife, happy life.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Come on, let's do it.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Why don't we leave your husband out of this for the time being?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "You're quite bossy, aren't you?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "But you see you did it.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Do you always get your own way?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "He's big, but he's very gentle.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "I mean, you boss him around?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have met Seal?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Four.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Because it felt like the pair of you had been sort of searching for each other and then you collided, and you have this extraordinary life with hundreds of children and fabulously successful careers?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Was it really?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "I was just visiting a friend.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "What were you both doing there?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I hadn't met him before.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "You knew him, right?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "And did he know you?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "I told him to sit down, have a pizza with us.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "So what happened next?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Literally, like that?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "And he hasn't got a clue you're Heidi Klum the supermodel?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "He doesn't know, seriously?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Then we met each other again, but always with friends.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "So what happens then?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "It went like this and normally we'd go and we just went like this.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "It was pretty good?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "We both gripped each other.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "And who gripped who?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I got really hot.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "And what were you thinking in that second?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I was like, oh, wow.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Did you think this is the guy?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Had you kissed lots of frogs to get to this point?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "So you squeeze hands, and then you get married.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Otherwise, things just don't get done, do they?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "He had an igloo built on a mountain?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "He just made something up.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Wait, what was the song?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "How could any woman resist this?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "\"Do you want to marry me?\"", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "And what were his exact words of proposal?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I said yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "And then nine months later Henry was born.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "And then what happened?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know how that happened.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "How do you be a mother to four children with everything else you do?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No, that's it", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Are there any more planned?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Do you like working with him?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "How do you keep this skinny figure that you have?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No way.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you started it would be nine seasons?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "-- right?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Did I pronounce that right?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Was that always the dream for you?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "You conquered the world of modeling, didn't you?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Every one and it still is, because everyone is a little step again.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "-- exciting moment for you?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "For this industry, yes, because the designers, such as him, they require the girls to be a certain weight, height and size.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Not thin enough and too short?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I mean, I --", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "And, also, it's dangerous sort of nonsense that he's starting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "I mean, there is a danger --", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "If I don't, I go back to Germany and I do something else, you know?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Any -- any scalpel at any stage?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I mean, I don't want to say never.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Would you ever?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Who are you doing it for?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Yes, I have --", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Is your great gift, if you like, the fact that you're secure in yourself, you're self-confident?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "That, too.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "You like making money, don't you?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I don't know if I'm that smart at it.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "ORGAN: Is that true?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I've been here since '94.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "-- keen to do that?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "That is a tough question.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I still am a German, as well.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "-- how do the Germans all feel when you when you became an American?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Oh, you are?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I have a dual citizenship.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Did you ever stop being a German?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I really like it.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What do you think of America?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "In Germany, definitely, yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Modern -- in the -- in the modern era, in the last sort of 30, 40 years?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "More designing.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "What's next for the Heidi Klum Incorporated machine?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "From the things -- yes, that I cook up.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I would not push them.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "-- to, any of them, to get into fashion, would you worry about it, given the experiences you've had?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "-- a rock star like their dad?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Oh, they're a lot of fun.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Well I -- I look forward to these kids growing up, actually, because they must -- they're going to look great and be very talented, aren't they?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "Oh, my family for sure.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "What's your proudest achievement, you personally?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "And you come home to a guy who just gets on bended knee in igloos and sings you crazy.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "And then what?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "We survived the '80s.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Who would've thought that to be 80s in Britain?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "But when you come to America now, how's it changed in all senses from when you first came out here?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Boring.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "How was L.A. when we first came here, first?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Andy Taylor, who was a guitarist with Duran Duran, was standing on top of the hotel where there's a pool.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "So how did you get kicked out?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "They haven't lived.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Modern bands just don't do this kind of thing, do they?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "E BON: Bloody jordies.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "Really you're not a proper rock star, right?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Vinyl is here, actually.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "How are you finding the changing style of music?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Well, ideally, I listen to music like that.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "How do you guys listen to music yourselves?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Do all of you do?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "It's better quality.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Why do you prefer it?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "It's a better sound.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Vinyl is better, is it?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "It's a ritual, putting it on, getting it oust sleeve, making sure that there's no fluff on it, and putting it on and putting the needle on.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Is it, really?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "We are.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "Are you guys on iTunes?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, there's been enormous problems with illegal downloads, which has affected the entire industry in a massive way.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "Or is all the money now just, from as I hear it, from touring and merchandise?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "Terrible.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "How did you -- when you came on stage, how did you feel?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "Well, actually, there was a middle person, Fiona, that Simon was living with.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 836, "question": "Which way around was it?", "qSentId": 835}, {"answer": "It was something a little opportunistic about that, I think.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "Or you never really crossed that barrier?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "Did he really?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "Well, I think really what Mark did was focus our attention on what we're good at.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 873, "question": "Or how did he revive the Duran magic, do you think?", "qSentId": 872}, {"answer": "He said you don't have to try, you just have to do what you do, and that's what people want from you.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "Was it reminding you, as a fan, was it reminding you of what you're all really good at, or was it making you more adaptable to the modern market?", "qSentId": 877}, {"answer": "Well, I think we were fortunate that we were a band, first of all, and that we always had each other.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 887, "question": "When you see what happened to Amy, what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 886}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 902, "question": "She got so thin, didn't she?", "qSentId": 901}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "Did you not?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "A mix.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 921, "question": "Are these old fans of yours who've come with you or do you have a new breed?", "qSentId": 920}, {"answer": "I think being a band goes beyond friendship, actually.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 971, "question": "We're never speaking again?", "qSentId": 970}, {"answer": "I think the keeping going and to create a body of work is one of the big ambitions.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 984, "question": "Do you have a genuine ambition, or is it to keep going?", "qSentId": 983}, {"answer": "I like the idea of it, but I think, one, it is very time consuming.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 998, "question": "Is it more of a primitive, because I would imagine you would be the first in that kind of stuff?", "qSentId": 997}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Coachella was great.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1005, "question": "Would you be in agreement you think?", "qSentId": 1004}, {"answer": "I think to that point --", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1012, "question": "Was it the best ever?", "qSentId": 1011}, {"answer": "You can't just pick one.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1014, "question": "ORGAN: Even at the height of the mania?", "qSentId": 1013}, {"answer": "Well, the Warren Cuccurullo.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1023, "question": "In Duran Duran history?", "qSentId": 1022}, {"answer": "Pink Flamingos.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1028, "question": "When was that?", "qSentId": 1027}, {"answer": "The groom wore more makeup than the bride.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1030, "question": "Pink Flamingo?", "qSentId": 1029}, {"answer": "It's a tattoo.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1038, "question": "I mean, you do for this show, but do you normally?", "qSentId": 1037}, {"answer": "If I feel like it, you never know.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1040, "question": "When you're going out, do you still get the old gear on?", "qSentId": 1039}, {"answer": "If I feel I need it, yes.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1044, "question": "Simon, do you?", "qSentId": 1043}, {"answer": "Well, I love --", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1052, "question": "Who is the best other singer you have ever seen live?", "qSentId": 1051}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111028pmt", "aSentId": 1062, "question": "It's all about now, isn't it?", "qSentId": 1061}]